SANUSI, ADEKUNLE TAOFEEK

E4/980k, LABOSINDE STREET, OLORUNSOGO IBADAN, OYO STATE, NIGFRIA

Tel; 2348033629353, 2348166072007

Email; adexsanusi@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a dedicated Technical Engineer with 5years of experience in industrial and Technology. My problem-solving skills and ability to manage high-pressure situation earned me employee of a year at Virgo Engineering Services and Construction company. My goal is to provide excellent service to each unique stakeholder across your company.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY, MINNA

B.Tech. in Industrial and Technology Education.

2014-2019

(Metal Work Technology

MUFUTAU OLANIHUN COMPREHENSIVE HIGH SCH. IBADAN

(SSCE Certificate). 2001-2007

PREVAILERS BAPTIST SCHOOL NUSERY/PRIMARY

1997-2001

(FSLC Certificate)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

VIRGO ENGINEERING SEEVICES NIGERIA LTD.| IBADAN

2019-2020

- Ensured appropriate supervision at the beginning of each day.
- Reported and responded to system failures immediately.
- Maintained and followed the preventative programs.
- Ensured that the facility and its equipment are properly maintained.
- Hand-on experience in conducting regular inspections.
- Ensured to keep working areas harzard-free and clean.

OUR LADY OF FATIMA CATHOLIC COLLEGE SCHOOL | KWARA STATE. 2020-2021

Junior secondary school (JSS) | Basic Technology Teacher

SKILLED ACQUIRED

- Knowledge ability about industrial safety, strength of material, and material technology.
- Proficiences in Microsoft Excel, Microsoft word office and Graphics Design.
- Effective Technical skills.
- Excellent organizational and time management skills.
- Ability to work a flexible schedule and handle multiple priorities.
- Ability to communicate in English (Verbally and Writing).

CERTIFICATIONS

- National Youth Service Corps.
- Graphics Design | CorelDrawn ii&iii, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word

REFEREES

Mr. Sanusi Adegun Ajani

Address: E4/980k, labosinde area, omowumi, ibadan.

Phone No: 08055694747

Dr. Yakub.I. Umar

Address: Head of section, Metal work Trchnology,

Department of Industrial and Technology Education, Federal University Of Technology,

Minna

Phone No: 08066059717

Mrs. Ogungbade Emmanuel

Address: Sole proprietor, Virgo Engineering services and Construction nigeria limited

Phone No: 08166072007